

4778 Canvasback Common Fremont, CA 94555 510-458-7112 mihir.mshah2@gmail.com

BIOGRAPHY

I'm 15 year old high school student and researcher from the cozy streets of Fremont. I have a few year's of experience in various fields, but I am mainly interested in trying new things. I am always looking for chances to develop new skills and learn.



EDUCATION

AMERICAN HIGH SCHOOL

FREMONT, CA | 10th Grade

Courses: Honors Chemistry | Honors English | Honors Algebra 2/Trigonometry | AP European History | Spanish 2 | Marketing | Physical Education

AMERICAN HIGH SCHOOL

FREMONT, CA | 9th Grade

Courses: Honors Biology | Honors English 9 | Honors Geometry | Spanish 1 | Physical Education | Health | Geography

AWARDS

DECA CALIFORNIA STATE COMPETITION | 2ND

SANTA CLARA, CA | MARCH 2017

Competed in the Entrepreneurship Promotion Project event. Promoted entrepreneurship to deaf students at the California School for the Deaf in Fremont, CA.

LEANGAP PITCH COMPETITION | 1ST

BOSTON, MA | Summer 2016

Pitched the Idea of ContaC, a company that creates elegant NFC-enabled business cards to increase the efficiency of contact sharing.

EXPERIENCE

RADIOLOGIO

LEAD DEVLEOPER | June 2017 - Present Worked with Professor Charles Lau on the development of Android applications in order to curate medical diagnoses and improve clinical outcomes to people already in the meidical field.

BIOENGINEERING HONOR SOCIETY

RESEARCH TEAM LEAD | January 2017 - April 2017 Created a minimally invasive method of detection for Eosinophilic Esophagitis using Krypton-81m radioactive tracer and Immuno-CAP allergen test to compete in the competition.

SUMMIT DIRECTOR | January 2017 - Present Organizing a summit for Generation Z entrepreneurs located in San Francisco. Delegating tasks and obtaining the majority of the sponsors.

BLUE OCEAN COMPETITION

COMMITTEE MEMBER | November 2016 - Present Organized a national entrepreneurship competition for high school students. Worked to obtain sponsors and speakers and marked the competition.

DECA CLUB

WRITTEN EVENT COORDINATOR | May 2017 - Present Developed a curriculum to teach members how to write effective business reporting techniques. Proofread and edited every member's written report.

CONTAC

CO-FOUNDER AND CEO | April 2016 - December 2016 Founded a company to create NFC-enabled business cards. Created the website and managed the entire team alongside email and social-media marketing of the product.

RESEARCH

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, SAN FRANCISCO

RESEARCHER | June 2017 - Present

Working on research for the development of novel methods for acquisition and analysis of Magnetic Resonance brain images, specifically targeting micro-bleeds formed in the brain after radiation therapy.

STANFORD UNIVERSITY

RESEARCHER | July 2017 - Present

Researching and developing an artificial intelligence to be applied to the modeling of drug behavior using Python and TensorFlow. Specifically focusing on anesthetic and analgesic drugs with Dr. Steven Shafer.